









CA, USA

anhnguyen19903@gmail.com

(714) 483 4589

http://dawnuxi.com

Design to empower people, solve human problems, and create delightful human-centric experience Passionate in AR/VR, Artificial Intelligence, and Data Visualization technology

Experienced in designing and developing website, mobile app, VR app and data visualization software Set a goal to design a collaborative innovative environment where everyone can come together and innovate.

Skills Tools

Sketching	Branding	Design Thinking	Photoshop	Proto.io
HTML5/CSS3	Content Strategy	3D Modeling	After Effects	Mapbox Studio
JQuery	Agile Development	3D Rendering	Illustrators	Framer
Prototyping	Interaction Design	Animation	Premiere	Origami
Usability Testing	Information Architecture	UI/UX	Sketch	Principle
A/B testing	Video Editing	VR/AR	Paper & Markers	Unity3D
Wireframing	Critical Thinking	D3	Dreamweaver	Invision
Analytics	User Research	React	Animate/Flash	Cinema4D
Personas	Motion Graphics	C#	Edge Animate	Solidworks

Experience

8/2018-Present Pro, UX & Data Viz Designer - Corelogic Innovation Lab Santa Monica, CA Leading Discovery and Framing Process for Business Intelligence products and Geospatial Visualization projects

Exploring and designing future innovative strategies for Big Data Visualization
Leading VR Experience projects and keeping Corelogic on the cutting edge of leverage technology
Leading design for the innovation team which is responsible for the future of Corelogic product
development

Working on CEO-driven vision projects

5/2018-Present Co-Founder, Chief Designer - Virtision.com

Leading and building UX and Agile practices for VR experience development
Building vision and exploring innovative opportunities for Virtision's growth
Working closely with designers and engineers from end-to-end product development

8/2017-5/2018 UI/UX & VR Design Engineer - Syngenta US Innovation Lab Champaign, IL Designed and built the lab to become an interactive environment for innovation Participated in brainstorming, ideation, and project development stage.

Conducted user experience research and designed web, mobile application, interactive interface Delivered high quality digital products and design strategies

5/2017-5/2018 UI/UX & VR Intern - National Center for Supercomputing Applications Champaign, IL Led and redesigned Advanced Visualization Lab's web interface to attract and engage the general public to computational scientific research and contents better

Designed user interface and produced high-quality prototypes for data visualization software collaboration with NASA.

Researched and designed Virtual Reality Controller and interfaces for AVL's Virtual Director software in order to improve Scientific Data Visualization Design's experience and workflows Produced a demo of AVL's works to show in SIGGRAPH 2017 and got featured on Discovery Channel Designed and developed Virtual Reality experience on WebVR platform to showcase dome view production

Conducted User Experience Research and user testing in order to deliver excellent design strategies

2016-2017 Video Producer & Motion Designer - University of Illinois Housing Champaign, IL Filmed and edited commercial and event videos as well as design and animated motion graphics for advertisement and marketing's projects

2011–2013 Front-End Web Developer - Maarka Data Solutions Irvine, CA Designed and developed better UX/UI on the company's old website

Education

University of Illinois, at Urbana-Champaign

Industrial Design - Class of 2018 with Honors Industrial Design Society of America | Member Design Nation 2018 | Fellow

Volunteer Experience

CUBE Consulting Firm | Design Consultant Siebel Center for Design | VR Designer

Awards

UIUC's Student Employee of the Year 2017-2018